在他卖给我和艾莫斯家具的时候
When he sold Amos and me our furniture.
那你和他的私人关系呢
Your personal relationship with him,
你能告诉陪审团是从什么时候开始的吗
you tell the jury when that began.
从有一天晚上我让他送我回家开始的
When l permitted him to escort me home one night,
我想我不会和他一起的
l don't think l would've gone with him
如果哈特那天早晨没和我吵架
If Mr. Hart and me hadn't quarreled that very morning.
吵架了
Quarreled?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
好的 我
Well, l
假设是他的错
supposed it was his fault.
哦 不 先生 是我的错
Oh, no, sir. lt was my fault.
我觉得是因为我不停的埋怨他
l supposed l just couldn't stop pestering him.
埋怨他 为什么呢
Pestering him? About what?
我不喜欢他在修车厂每天工作那么多时间
l didn't like him working those long hours at the garage.
我想他在家里陪着我
l wanted him home with me...